John N. Rowe III papers, Inclusive: 1510-1989, undated, Bulk: 1830-1880
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Early Texas Documents, 1801-1989, undated; 2
  - Financial, 1802-1925, undated; 3
    The third subseries, financial, is made up of financial documents in the form of treasury warrants, inventories, receipts, bonds, Republic of Texas and Civil War currency, and checks. As with the other subseries in this section, most of the documents are stand alone items and have no connection to others in the subseries. The Republic of Texas and Civil War currency are interesting for the range and variety of notes.
    - Financial: Blank Confederate States Treasury Warrant, 1860’s (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Financial: Abercrombie, C.A., I.H. Thomason, A.R. Bowen-treasury warrant, 1862 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Abuey, J.C. -special treasury warrant, 1856 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Adam, Emil, H.B. Quimby Invoice of Subsistence Stores of 39th U.S. Infantry, 1868 January 3 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Adams, C.W., 1854-1860 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Adams, Sylvester -treasury warrant, 1836 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Addy, John, 1838 April 9 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Adsit, E.M. Thomas, 1851 September 26 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Financial: Adsit, George S., 1854 March 4 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Adsit, George S., 1855 May 29 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Adsit, George S., A.C. Crawford, 1857 December 28 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Allcorn, John H-Sterns & Lynch, 1852 April 9 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Financial: Allen, Ebenezer, Julius Kauffman, 1845 July 29 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Financial: Alley, Abraham, 1840 May (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Financial: Amos, M.V.-tax receipts, 1862 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Amos, M.V., A.I. Owens, -Confederate war tax, 1863 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Anderson, K.L. (Kenneth Lewis), 1845 June 16 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Anderson, Levi, Faukersley Bros.- receipt, 1887 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Financial: Anderson, Robert D. and Mavis May [various dates on note from 1840-1849], 1849 September (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Andrews and Grover, 1854 March 15 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Financial: Andrews, Edmond, 1837, November 10 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Andrews, E.B., E. Martin & H.A. Cobb, 1846 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Andrews, H.B., P. Reynaud, 1858 November 8 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Andrews, Henry B., Benjamin F. Batchelor, John M. Reed, 1856 July 19 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Financial: Anonymous, undated (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Financial: Aoses, George S., 1855 September (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Financial: Appleby, Bob, John Callier, Nebraska Bridge Supply, Stanton County Treasury Warrant, 1900 March 20 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Financial: Appleby, Bob Chas P. Jones, A.C. Hanff, Stanton County Treasury Warrant, 1899 November 15 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Financial: Appleby, Bob, John Callier, C.A. Mewis, Stanton County Treasury Warrant, 1900 March 20 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Financial: Armstrong, Audrey- military certificate, 1836 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Financial: Armstrong, John and F.A. Walley & CO., 1847 April (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Financial: Arrowood, Hillman, M.W. Hammock, C.N. Randolph, Clement R. Johns, F.R. Lubbock, Treasury Warrant, 1861 November 16 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Financial: Ashton, William Jr., Thomas M. Joseph, 1852 August 21 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Financial: Atwater, John, Charles Atwater, 1839 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Financial: Austin, Henry, M.C. Hudson, 1836 November 4 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Financial: Austin, Henry, Gail Borden, Jr., 1836 November 4 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Financial: Austin, Henry, Mr. Shaw, 1848 June 22 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Financial: Austin, Henry, James F. Perry, William Perry, Gail Borden, Jr., Charles Hoffman, George Cook, N. Edwards, 1847 June 16 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Financial: Austin, M., Francis Janius, 1802 June 21 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Financial: Austin, Stephen F, 1825 February 20 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Financial: Ayers, David, Samuel P. Brown, 1835 August 1 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Financial: Ayres, David, Atwood, Baines Farmer & Company-promissory note, 1854 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Financial: Ayers, David, L. Edgerton & Doane, 1854 March 18 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Financial: Ayres vs. Beaman, undated (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Financial: B, Bennett M.- military certificate, 1836 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Financial: Bade, William F., 1858 October (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Financial: Bade, William F., 1859 November (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Financial: Bailey, Alphonso P., Atkins, Stedman & Company, 1853 August 27 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Financial: Bailey, Alphonso P., Dulton Richardson & Company, 1854 March 25 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Financial: Bailey, Alphonso P., Lucas Comstock, 1853 July 14 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Financial: Bailey, W.- treasury warrant, 1836 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Financial: Baldwin, H. (Estate of), H.S. Conner, John L. Sleight, J.H. Brown, 1850 November 10 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - Financial: Ball, A.H., William Cotton, 1844 October 10 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - Financial: Ball, George, A.C. Crawford, A. Baldinger, Luke Bryan, E. Lewis, 1847 January 1 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - Financial: Ball, Hutchings & Company, Blank Bank Check, 187[ ] (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Financial: Bar, John A., Nancy Bar Hodges, 1849 April 3 (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - Financial: Barclay, D.M., George L. Durham, C.N. Randolph, Treasury Warrant, 1861 February 11 (Box 30, Folder 57)
    - Financial: Barhydt, D.P., Musgrove Evans- auditor’s certificate, 1840 (Box 30, Folder 58)
    - Financial: Barnard, Henrietta, E.P. Hunt, 1854 March 31 (Box 30, Folder 59)
    - Financial: Bartholomew, E.C.-tax redemption receipt, 1878 (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - Financial: Bartlett, James, Kidder Walker, undated (Box 30, Folder 61)
    - Financial: Barttell, Joseph, William P. Huff, 1838 May 22 (Box 30, Folder 62)
    - Financial: Baumgarten, F.W., Alfred F. James, 1847 January 1 (Box 30, Folder 63)
    - Financial: Baumgarten, F.W. and Jacuh Susse, 1847 December (Box 30, Folder 64)
    - Financial: Baylor, R.E.B.- treasury warrant, 1844, 1863 (Box 30, Folder 65)
    - Financial: Baylor, R.E.B., 1862 January 22 (Box 30, Folder 66)
    - Financial: Beal, William M., 1838, 1839 (Box 30, Folder 67)
    - Financial: Beal, W.M.-promissory note, 1859 (Box 30, Folder 68)
    - Financial: Beck, Cass-promissory note, 1844 (Box 30, Folder 69)
    - Financial: Beckwith, Bol. Major Generall. A., H.B. Quimby, Invoice of Subsistence Stores, 1868 March 10 (Box 30, Folder 70)
    - Financial: Bee, H.P., George B. Erath, Promissory Note to George B. Erath, 1838 January 19 (Box 30, Folder 71)
    - Financial: Beissner, C.L., I. Fessenden, John & Cornelius O’Conner, 1857 February 2 (Box 30, Folder 72)
    - Financial: Bell, Vincent, Circa 1840 March 12 (Box 30, Folder 73)
    - Financial: Benedict Hall & Company, Anderson & Phalen, 1860 August 4 (Box 30, Folder 74)
    - Financial: Benedict, J.W., T.W. Murray, 1846 Fall Term (Box 30, Folder 75)
    - Financial: Benhard, H.- warrant, 1867 (Box 30, Folder 76)
    - Financial: Bennett, J.H., 1853 June 17 (Box 30, Folder 77)
    - Financial: Bennett, John H., H.G. Barnard, 1853 August 2 (Box 30, Folder 78)
    - Financial: Bennett, John H., H.T. Barnard, 1853 February 2 (Box 30, Folder 79)
    - Financial: Bennett, John H., Stacy B. and Allen Lewis, Lent M. Hitchcock, Stephen VanSickle, 1852 April 28 (Box 30, Folder 80)
    - Financial: Bennett, John H., William A. Gold, T.F. Hollis, 1848 August 2 (Box 30, Folder 81)
    - Financial: Bensemann, Herman, C.H., Randolph, Clement R. Johns, George L. Durham, Treasury Warrant, 1860 February 11 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Financial: Benson, Herman, 1850 August 2 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Benton & Bell, William W. Bell, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Berkmeir, Thomas and William B. Kramer, 1863 February (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Bernard, Geo., H.S. Denison, C.H. Randolph, J.W. Howard, Treasury Warrant, 1865 January 16 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Berry, David, Jackson C.C. Smith, 1848 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Berry, David, J.C.C. Smith, 1849-1851 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Berry, H.W., F.G. Estrange- treasury warrant, 1861 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Financial: Berry, W.B., 1842 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Biddle, Thomas A.- consolidated fund, 1847 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Billingsby, I. A. -Treasury Warrant, 1861 February 8 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Birdsall, John- stock certificate, 1839 March (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Financial: Cap. Bishop, Philip W. McLaughlin, James Blair, and John Wright, 1839 May (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Financial: Black, John, James T. Pruitt, 1838 December 25 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Financial: Blank Promissory Notes from The Republic of Texas, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Blick, William- promissory note, 1838 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Blondeau, P.F., William E. Dowert, 1853 November 17 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Board, A.- treasury warrant, 1837 June 15 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Financial: Bolton, Charles S.- Tax Receipts, 1871-1872 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Bolton, C.L., Walter Gresham, Henry K. Mann, 1874 October 31 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Financial: Borden, Gail Jr., 1836 January (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Borden, Gail Jr.- stock certificate, 1839 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Borden, Gail Jr., David G. Burnet, 1851 January 29 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Borden Jr., Gail, D.S. Kelsey, P. Edmonds, 1841, 1845 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Financial: Borden, Gail Jr., Galveston City Company, William B. Nicholos, 1839 October 25 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Financial: Borden, Gail Jr., John P. Borden, M.S. Sitts, Estate of Peter W. Grayson, 1846 April 28 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Financial: Borden, Thomas H., Gail Borden Jr., 1836 July 20 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Financial: Borland, Abraham, Levi [illegible], 1819 July 24 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Financial: Bostick, Leon, undated (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Financial: Bostwick, J.L. and Joshua C. Shaw, 1850 Aug (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Financial: Bostick, W., John Hunter, 1827 March 26 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Financial: Boyd, J.B.- special treasury warrant, 1859 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Financial: Bransam, Martha, Levi Bostick, undated (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Financial: Brayher, J.P., 1844 February (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Financial: Bremond, Paul, Estate of John Watson, 1840 June 6 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Financial: Brenham, Washington County Script (Blank), circa 1860’s (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Financial: Brenham, Washington County Script, M.N. Horton, 1862 July 6 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Financial: Briggs, J.L., 1876 June 30 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Financial: Brigham, A., Alfred Swingle, H.C. Hendson, Promissory note payable to Alfred Swingle, 1836 September 4 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Financial: Brigham, A., E. Morehouse, 1844 March 26 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Financial: Brigham, Asa, Edmond Andrews, 1844 April 15 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Financial: Brock, Johnathan, Elisha O. Lynch, 1851 May 22 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Financial: Brown, Benjamin- treasury warrant, 1837 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Financial: Brown, Joseph F., Isaac Fessinder, C.L. Beissner, 1845 January 5 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Financial: Brown, Joseph M., C.H. Randolph, Clement R. Johns, 1858 February 15 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Financial: Brown, Lewis B., Charles D. Sayre, George Butler, 1859 January 15 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Financial: Brown, M.J., J.G. Scruggs, C.N. Randolph, Jal. V. Holingwath, 1863 July 11 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Financial: Brummell, Inos and Nathaniel A., Ware, 1850 October (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - Financial: Bryan, J.P., 1844 (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - Financial: Bryan, Jacob, 1852 December 2 (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - Financial: Bryan, Jacob, undated (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - Financial: Bryan, M.A., James H. Jones, 1879 May 9 (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - Financial: Bryan, William, Boyes, Robert H., Adolphe Mazunan, 1836 June 18 (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - Financial: Bryan, William J., Thomas Lewis, 1859 September 19 (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - Financial: Bullock, C.W., 1860 (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - Financial: Burgher, J.P. and S. Swartz, 1844 July (Box 31, Folder 56)
    - Financial: Burger, Joseph P., Ambrose Hall, 1844 July 22 (Box 31, Folder 57)
    - Financial: Burger, J.P. and E.S. Wood, 1844 July (Box 31, Folder 58)
    - Financial: Burger, Joseph P., G.A. Branan, 1844 July 22 (Box 31, Folder 59)
    - Financial: Burger, J.P., L.M. Hitchcock, undated (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - Financial: Burke, James W., Gal: Houston & H.R.R. Company, undated (Box 31, Folder 61)
    - Financial: Burleson, James, 1844 (Box 31, Folder 62)
    - Financial: Burman, Jesse, Isham (Isam) Sims, 1841 May 19 (Box 31, Folder 63)
    - Financial: Burner, J.H., M.L. Bobb, H. Roye, 1893 October 4-December 12 (Box 31, Folder 64)
    - Financial: Burris, Benjamin, Adaline Burris, Sister Saint J. de Chantal, 1856 April 24 (Box 31, Folder 65)
    - Financial: Bush, R.S., 1860 (Box 31, Folder 66)
    - Financial: Butler, Jonas, James Love, Toby vs. David Kendan, 1859 July 4 (Box 31, Folder 67)
    - Financial: Byrne, Byrne & Mark, undated (Box 31, Folder 68)
    - Financial: Cabaness, John C., 1861 (Box 31, Folder 69)
    - Financial: Cabell, W. L., J. K. Rose, 1889 May 9 (Box 31, Folder 70)
    - Financial: Caldwell, P., A. Houston, 1836 March 11 (Box 31, Folder 71)
    - Financial: Callaway, Willis F., 1837 January (Box 31, Folder 72)
    - Financial: Caller, S.S., George J. Becker, 1840 September 15 (Box 31, Folder 73)
    - Financial: Camp Hudson, Texas, 1860 (Box 31, Folder 74)
    - Financial: Campbell, J.J., John Ireland, 1861 (Box 31, Folder 75)
    - Financial: Cannon, William P., 1840 (Box 31, Folder 76)
    - Financial: Cardova, R.D., 1864 (Box 31, Folder 77)
    - Financial: Carlston, Henry, 1844 (Box 31, Folder 78)
    - Financial: Carly, William, 1861 (Box 31, Folder 79)
    - Financial: Carothers, T.-treasury warrant, 1863 Janaury 13 (Box 31, Folder 80)
    - Financial: Carpenter, L. A.-treasury warrant, 1862 (Box 31, Folder 81)
    - Financial: Carroll, F., Nye E. Schneider Company, Louis Smithbuger, 1893 January 6 (Box 31, Folder 82)
    - Financial: Caruthers, Allen and Young Caruthers, 1840 September (Box 31, Folder 83)
    - Financial: Casey, Sam., Swen Magnus Swenson, Y. Bigger, J.H. Brown, R.H. Sonny, 1856 June 28 (Box 31, Folder 84)
    - Financial: Castleman, Andrew, N. Townsend, 1832 August 11 (Box 31, Folder 85)
    - Financial: Cator, A.J.-receipt for poll tax, 1908 November 4 (Box 31, Folder 86)
    - Financial: Cator, Edith M., James H. Cator, 1908 June 25 (Box 31, Folder 87)
    - Financial: Cator, James F., James H. Cator, 1911 December 1 (Box 31, Folder 88)
    - Financial: Cator, James H., George Poell, 1894 July 6 (Box 31, Folder 89)
    - Financial: Cator, James H., James H. Cator, 1914 December 31 (Box 31, Folder 90)
    - Financial: Cator, James H., W. B. Narkham, 1888 August 13 (Box 31, Folder 91)
    - Financial: Cator, James H., Z. A. Curtis, 1896 December 21 (Box 31, Folder 92)
    - Financial: Cator, James, James Jelanager, 1909 July 11 (Box 31, Folder 93)
    - Financial: Cator, James H. W. H. Crawford, 1918 September 30 (Box 31, Folder 94)
    - Financial: Cator, J.H., Bonner Loan & Investment Company, 1919 November 21 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Financial: Cator, J.H., Bert Cator, 1908 November 4 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Cator, Mrs. James H., James H. Cator, 1916 September 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Cayce, H.P., 1838 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Cecil, Joseph, S. Moore, H.W. Raglin, 1844 February (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Chambers, William, J.C. Keuhn, Thomas Salter, A.H. Ladd, Doswell, Hill & Company, 1854 March 7 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Chambers, William, J.C. Keuhn, Doswell, Hill & Company, 1853 December 20 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Chapman, J., 1863 September 10 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Financial: Chapmen, J.H.F., John P. Davie, 1849 April 12 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Checks, A.T. Amed, M.C. Rector, 1902 November 4 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Cheltenham and Abington Sewerage Company, 1900s (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Chesholm, J.M.H., C.N. Randolph, 1862 December 22 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Financial: Choate, Moses L., John P. Davie, 1854 March 8 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Financial: Christian, Martin, 1836 October 22 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Financial: City of Portland, Texas-stock certificate, 1841 April 29 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Clapper, Nicholas, E.E. Este, 1841 April 29 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Clark, Captain Jonathan, E.G. Shipp, 1843 September 20 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Cleveland, Israel, 1860 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Financial: Close, Hiram, John Gladwin, 1839 December 23 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Cock, W.F., 1837 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Financial: Coleman, F.D.-Tellico Manufacturing Company, 1857 September (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Collier, T.T., 1844 November 2 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Collin County, C.H. Randolph, 1863 December 15 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Collins, Daniel, 1837 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Financial: Collins, Stephen, 1838 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Financial: Colton, Williams, J.L. Lynon, 1849 January (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Financial: Commercial and Agriculture Bank, 1850 April 3, May 1 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Financial: Confederate Tax Receipts, 1862, 1864-1867 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Financial: Conroy, Peter, 1846 March 5 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Financial: Conroy, Peter, 1849 June 14 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Financial: Cook, William, Wilson & Davie, 1840 July 13 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Financial: Corzine, Shelby, 1836 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Financial: Costby, Captain Michael, 1836 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Financial: Cowan, D.C., C.N. Randolph, Edward Clark, 1861 May 31 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Financial: Crawford, A.C., 1845 November 8 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Financial: Crecy, J.-Caravansary, 1841, April-June (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Financial: Crim, D.M., 1843 July 31 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Financial: Criswell, John Y., 1839 December (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Financial: Criswell, L.N., 1845 November 29 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Financial: Criswell, J.V., John Y. Criswell, 1842 May 3 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Financial: Crook, L.N., A. Foster, C.N. Randolph, C.R. Johns, 1863 November 20 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Financial: Cross, William, 1847 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Financial: Cullen, Ezekial, H.T. Culling, T.J. Brooks, 1846 November 18 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Financial: Cummins, C.-Caravansary, 1841 April-June (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Financial: Cushman-Caravansary, 1841 April-June (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Financial: Dailey, R., W.K. Evans, N.K. Kellums, 1840 December (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Financial: Dailey, Raymond, Donald McDonald, 1843 November 28 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Financial: Dangerfield, William H., Duer & Lubbock, 1842 December 13 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Financial: Daniels, Charles, 1841 August 7 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Financial: Davie, John P., William R. Wilson, David S. Kelsey, William E. Ban, 1840 March 30 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Financial: Davis, S., Joseph Durst, David Montier, 1846 September (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Financial: Davidson, Margaret, 1837 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Financial: Davis, James, F.S. Estrange, 1861 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Financial: Day, W.S., A.C. Horton, undated (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Financial: Dean, John, 1861 February 21 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Financial: Dean, John-tax receipt, 1859 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Financial: Dean, John, Jacob L. Briggs, 1859 July 20 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Financial: Dean, John, J.W. Pilant, 1861 May 10 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Financial: Dean, John, J.W. Pilant, Jr., E.D. Hamner, 1859 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - Financial: Dean, John, Willis Pilant, 1860 (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Financial: Dearborn, M.H.-Caravansary, 1841 May (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Financial: Deats, W.S., George Ball, 1855 July 19 (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Financial: de Cordova & Davison, F.D. Lewis, 1840 October 6 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Financial: de Cordova, Jacob, 1848 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Financial: DeMorse, Charles, 1841-1846 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Financial: Densman, James, 1837 (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Financial: Derrick, J.A., M.F. Locke, C.N. Randolph, George L. Durham, 1860 (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Financial: DeWolf, Samuel, 1841 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Financial: DeWolf, Samuel, Piper and Lynch, 1840 May 29 (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Financial: Dexter, Andrew, 1818 (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Financial: DeYoung, John, Mrs. Poulilcan, 1843 March 15 (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - Financial: Dickenson, Edmond, 1837 (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - Financial: Dillard, A.B., J. Kerly McCurd, C.N. Randolph, Clement R. Johns, 1861 June 7 (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - Financial: Dimitt, Philip & Company, LaVaca, Thomas Powell, Joseph Caseano, 1836 September 15 (Box 32, Folder 74)
    - Financial: Dimitt, Philip & Company, LaVaca, Thomas Powell, Nathaniel Lewis, 1836 September 16 (Box 32, Folder 75)
    - Financial: Dimitt, Philip & Company, LaVaca, Thomas Powell, William Bracking, 1836 September 16 (Box 32, Folder 76)
    - Financial: Dimitt, Philip & Company, LaVaca, Thomas Powell, William Trapnall, 1837 April 25 (Box 32, Folder 77)
    - Financial: Dimitt, P., Thomas Powell, J.C. Perce, 1837 June 15 (Box 32, Folder 78)
    - Financial: Dimitt, P., Thomas Powell, William Bracking, 1837 July 3 (Box 32, Folder 79)
    - Financial: Dimitt, Philip, Thomas Powell, Benjamin Perkins, 1837 July 12 (Box 32, Folder 80)
    - Financial: Dimitt, P., Thomas Powell, 1838 August 5 (Box 32, Folder 81)
    - Financial: Doswell, Richardson & Company, William Manor, 1854 April 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Financial: Duclose, Sarah, C. Poullalin, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Duncan, A., 1862 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Duncan, James, 1836 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Durham, George, J.R. Wooldridge, 1844 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Dyer, Isadore A., 1853 December (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Financial: E.O. Lynch & Company, Palmer & Luce, 1851 March 7 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Earp, Ellender, William Earp, 1844 June 29 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Financial: Earp, Ellender, W.W. Earp, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Earp, Ellender Dixon, William Earp, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Earp, Ichabod C., undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Earp, William, 1843 January 9 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Financial: Earp, William, 1844 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Financial: Earp, William, 1844 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Financial: Earp, William, 1844 February (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Earp, William, Ichabod C. Earp, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Eccly, J.G., 1837 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Edmundson, John L., H.F. James, J.H. Raymond, 1858 December 6 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Financial: Edwards, Monroe, undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Edwards, Peyton, Lelia and Clara, 1883-1884 (Box Financial: 33, Folder 20)
    - Financial: Edwards, Powell R., E.F. Green, Oscar Farish, 1854 January 13 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Edwards, Powell R., Fredrich Vornbaumen, J.H. Linder, 1853 January 17 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Edwards, W.C., G.H. Edwards, 1838 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Eglantine, Schooner, 1850 September 4 (Box 33, Folder 24)